TuftScope: The Interdisciplinary Journal of Health, Ethics and Policy UP226
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
TuftScope: The Interdisciplinary Journal of Health, Ethics and Policy
2001 -- 2019
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Community Union Senate
UP226
1 Linear Feet
17 Digital Object(s)
1 Web sites
This collection contains issues of TuftScope: The Interdisciplinary Journal of Health, Ethics and Policy, and web crawls documenting its web presence.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: TuftScope and Web crawls.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of TuftScope: The Interdisciplinary Journal of Health, Ethics and Policy, and web crawls documenting its web presence. It was originally published in 2001 as a student publication of Tufts-AMSA. It is currently a separate student organization of Tufts University funded by the TCU Senate.
Biographical / Historical
Established in 1968, the Tufts Community Union (TCU) Senate is the student parliament and legislative/executive body of TCU Student Government for the undergraduate students of the College of Liberal Arts and Jackson College and the College of Engineering. As of Spring 2000, it is charged with representing the needs and interests of the TCU before the faculty of the undergraduate colleges, the administration, and the Trustees of Tufts College. Through the Treasury, it oversees the use of the student activities fee and ensures that the needs and interests of the students are voiced.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
- TuftScope, 2001 -- 2019; UP226.001.000001; 1 Linear Feet; 17 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  TuftScope is the interdisciplinary journal of health, ethics, and policy. It is funded in part by the Tufts University Student Life Fund and Tufts Biology Department.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - TuftScope, 2001; UP226.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Volume, issue
    1, 1
    Ethics; Health policy; Tufts University
  - TuftScope, 2001; UP226.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    1, 2
    Health policy; Ethics; Tufts University
  - TuftScope, 2002; UP226.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    2, 1
  - TuftScope, 2003; UP226.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    3, 1
  - TuftScope, 2004; UP226.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    Volume
    4
  - TuftScope, Spring, 2006; UP226.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    5
  - TuftScope, Spring, 2007; UP226.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    6
  - TuftScope, Winter, 2007 -- 2008; UP226.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    7
  - TuftScope, Spring, 2008; UP226.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    7, 2
    Health policy; Ethics; Publications; Tufts University
  - TuftScope, Fall, 2008; UP226.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    8, 1
  - TuftScope, Spring, 2009; UP226.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    8, 2
  - TuftScope, Fall, 2009; UP226.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    9, 1
  - TuftScope, Spring, 2010; UP226.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    9, 2
  - TuftScope, Fall, 2010; UP226.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    10, 1
  - TuftScope, Winter, 2011; UP226.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    10, 2
  - TuftScope, Spring, 2011; UP226.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
    10, 3
  - TuftScope, Fall, 2011; UP226.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
    11, 1
  - TuftScope, Spring, 2012; UP226.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
    11, 2
  - TuftScope, Summer/Fall, 2012; UP226.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
    12, 1
  - TuftScope, Fall, 2012; UP226.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
    12, 2
  - TuftScope, Spring, 2013; UP226.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
    12, 4
  - TuftScope, Fall, 2013; UP226.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
    13, 1
  - TuftScope, Spring, 2014; UP226.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
    13, 2
  - TuftScope, Fall, 2014; UP226.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
    14, I
  - TuftScope, Spring, 2015; UP226.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
    14, II
  - TuftScope, Fall, 2015; UP226.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
    15, I
  - TuftScope, Spring, 2016; UP226.001.000002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Volume, Issue
    15, II
  - TuftScope, Spring, 2017; UP226.001.001.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 28)
    16, II
  - TuftScope, Fall 2017; UP226.000035 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    17, 1
  - TuftScope, Spring, 2018; UP226.001.001.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 29)
    17, II
  - TuftScope, Fall, 2018; UP226.001.001.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Volume, Number
    18, 01
  - TuftScope, Spring 2019; UP226.000036 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    18, II
  - TuftScope, Fall 2019; UP226.000037 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    19, 1
- Web crawls, 2015 -- 2019; UP226.002; 1 Web sites
  Quarterly web crawls of the TuftScope website crawled by DCA, as part of the Student Organizations web collection, to document the presesence of Tufts University student organizations on the web.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Student Organizations web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/6387
  - TuftScope, 2015-09-23 -- 2019-11-15; UP226.002.00001
    Accruals
    URL updated to http://tuftscope.squarespace.com/ from http://tuftscope.blogspot.com/ on September 13, 2017 by Margaret Peachy.